<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on Securely using Cryptography with CogniCrypt</title><link>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/</link><description>Recent content in News on Securely using Cryptography with CogniCrypt</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Eclipse Foundation)</managingEditor><webMaster>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Eclipse Foundation)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 16:30:13 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ph.D. Thesis on CogniCrypt Published!</title><link>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/ph.d.-thesis-on-cognicrypt-published/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 16:30:13 +0200</pubDate><author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Eclipse Foundation)</author><guid>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/ph.d.-thesis-on-cognicrypt-published/</guid><description>We are happy to announce the publication of Stefan Krüger&amp;rsquo;s Ph.D. Thesis! The thesis gives a comprehensive introduction into CogniCrypt and the research we have been conducting over the past few years in the context of the tool. In the thesis, Krüger motivates the work on CogniCrypt and discusses the approach, comprising of CrySL, CogniCryptSAST, and CogniCryptGEN, in detail. That is not all, however. In the final chapters of the thesis, Krüger also outlines several ideas for further CrySL-based tool support that should help developers use cryptographic APIs and that are already in the works.</description></item><item><title>CogniCrypt 1.0 released!</title><link>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/cognicrypt-1.0-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 15:03:13 +0200</pubDate><author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Eclipse Foundation)</author><guid>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/cognicrypt-1.0-released/</guid><description>Researchers from the Collaborative Research Center CROSSING and partners are working on crypto assistant for software developers
CogniCrypt supports developers during the integration of cryptographic components into software and checks automatically if they are integrated and configured correctly. After five years of work, CogniCrypt has matured to Version 1.0. For this release, we have extended and thoroughly tested CogniCrypt&amp;rsquo;s main features: the code generator and the static code analysis. CogniCrypt now supports the code generation for five widely found cryptographic use cases, Data Encryption, Secure Communication, Secure Password Storage, Long-Term Archiving, and Multi-party computation.</description></item><item><title>VIM Syntax highlighting</title><link>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/vim-syntax-highlighting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:03:13 +0200</pubDate><author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Eclipse Foundation)</author><guid>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/vim-syntax-highlighting/</guid><description>Thanks to Theofilos Petsios from Amazon Web Services for providing a definition file for syntax highlighting for CrySL in VIM. You can download the definitions here.</description></item><item><title>Job Offerings</title><link>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/job-offerings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 18:03:13 +0200</pubDate><author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Eclipse Foundation)</author><guid>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/job-offerings/</guid><description>We currently have several openings for full-time research staff and software developers who will help us bring CogniCrypt to the next level. The openings are located both at Paderborn and Darmstadt. Please contact Eric Boddenfor further information.</description></item><item><title>CogniCrypt being presented at Heise devSec</title><link>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/cognicrypt-being-presented-at-heise-devsec/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 18:03:13 +0200</pubDate><author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Eclipse Foundation)</author><guid>https://www.eclipse.org/cognicrypt/news/cognicrypt-being-presented-at-heise-devsec/</guid><description>CogniCrypt is being presented in a full-day workshop and a conference talk at this year&amp;rsquo;s Heise devSec!</description></item></channel></rss>